toolkit_default = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "axis": "AXIS 1. GROUNDWORK",
        "axis_score": 0,
        "axis_completion": 0,
        "domains": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 1: PARAMETERS OF SCALE",
                "domain_max": 2,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "1-1",
                        "question_max": 2,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None],
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 2: CONTEXTUAL ENVIRONMENT",
                "domain_max": 22,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "2-1",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "2-2",
                        "question_max": 8,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "2-3",
                        "question_max": 8,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 3: SCIENTIFIC BASIS",
                "domain_max": 30,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "3-1a",
                        "question_max": 8,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "3-1b",
                        "question_max": 4,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "3-2",
                        "question_max": 18,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None, None]
                    },
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "axis": "AXIS 2. PARTNERSHIPS",
        "axis_score": 0,
        "axis_completion": 0,
        "domains": [
            {
                "id": 4,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 4: STRATEGIC ENGAGEMENT",
                "domain_max": 48,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "4-1a",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None],
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "4-1b",
                        "question_max": 27,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None, None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "4-2",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None],
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 5: PARTNERSHIP SUSTAINABILITY",
                "domain_max": 50,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "5-1a",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "5-1b",
                        "question_max": 10,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "5-1c",
                        "question_max": 10,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "5-2a",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "5-2b",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "axis": "AXIS 3. FINANCIAL HEALTH",
        "axis_score": 0,
        "axis_completion": 0,
        "domains": [
            {
                "id": 6,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 6: FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT",
                "domain_max": 45,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "6-1",
                        "question_max": 18,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None, None],
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "6-2",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None]
                    }, {
                        "question": "6-3",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "6-4",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None],
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 7: FINANCIAL MODEL",
                "domain_max": 36,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "7-1",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "7-2",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "7-3",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "axis": "AXIS 4. TECHNOLOGY & ARCHITECTURE",
        "axis_score": 0,
        "axis_completion": 0,
        "domains": [
            {
                "id": 8,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 8: DATA",
                "domain_max": 43,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "8-1",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None],
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "8-2",
                        "question_max": 18,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None, None]
                    }, {
                        "question": "8-3a",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "8-3b",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None],
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 9: INTEROPERABILITY",
                "domain_max": 18,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "9-1",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "9-2",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 10: ADAPTABILITY",
                "domain_max": 30,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "10-1",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "10-2",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "10-3",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None]
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "axis": "AXIS 5. OPERATIONS",
        "axis_score": 0,
        "axis_completion": 0,
        "domains": [
            {
                "id": 11,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 11: PERSONNEL",
                "domain_max": 33,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "11-1",
                        "question_max": 21,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None, None, None],
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "11-2",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 12: TRAINING AND SUPPORT",
                "domain_max": 45,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "12-1a",
                        "question_max": 15,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "12-1b",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "12-2",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "12-3",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 13: OUTREACH AND SENSITIZATION",
                "domain_max": 15,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "13-1",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None],
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "13-2",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None]
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 14: CONTINGENCY PLANNING",
                "domain_max": 18,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "14-1",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None],
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "14-2",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    }
                ]
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "axis": "AXIS 6. MONITORING & EVALUATION",
        "axis_score": 0,
        "axis_completion": 0,
        "domains": [
            {
                "id": 15,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 15: PROCESS MONITORING",
                "domain_max": 25,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "15-1a",
                        "question_max": 4,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None],
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "15-1b",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "15-2",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "domain": "DOMAIN 16: EVALUATION RESEARCH",
                "domain_max": 66,
                "domain_sum": 0,
                "domain_percentage": 0,
                "domain_completion": 0,
                "questions": [
                    {
                        "question": "16-1a",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "16-1b",
                        "question_max": 9,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "16-1c",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "16-2a",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "16-2b",
                        "question_max": 12,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "16-2c",
                        "question_max": 15,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None, None, None, None]
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "16-3",
                        "question_max": 6,
                        "question_sum": 0,
                        "answers": [None, None]
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
]
